{"game_code":"249DHJ51","level_name":"test1","questions":[{"answer":"Class A","incorrect":["Class B","Class C","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the range from 1.0.0.1 to 126.255.255.254 fall?"},{"answer":"Class B","incorrect":["Class A","Class C","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the range from 128.1.0.1 to 191.255.255.254 fall?"},{"answer":"Class C","incorrect":["Class A","Class B","Class E"],"question":"In which IP address class does the range from 192.0.1.1 to 223.255.254.254 fall?"},{"answer":"Class D","incorrect":["Class B","Class C","Class E"],"question":"In which IP address class does the range from 224.0.0.0 to 239.255.255.255 fall?"},{"answer":"Network ID","incorrect":["Node ID","Class ID","Address ID"],"question":"It tells us which network the device is part of"},{"answer":"Node ID","incorrect":["Network ID","Class ID","Address ID"],"question":"It identifies that unique device within the network"},{"answer":"255.0.0.0","incorrect":["255.255.0.0","255.255.255.0","255.255.255.255"],"question":"What is the default subnet mask for Class A IP address?"},{"answer":"255.255.0.0","incorrect":["255.255.255.0","255.0.0.0","255.255.255.255"],"question":"What is the default subnet mask for Class B IP address?"},{"answer":"255.255.255.0","incorrect":["255.255.0.0","255.0.0.0","255.255.255.255"],"question":"What is the default subnet mask for Class C IP address?"},{"answer":"Class C","incorrect":["Class A","Class B","Class D"],"question":"In which IP address class does the address 192.168.10.1 belong?"},{"answer":"249.155.251.15","incorrect":["128.64.32.16","255.255.255.255","249.155.250.1"],"question":"What is the dotted-decimal notation for the binary IP address: 11111001 10011011 11111011 00001111 ?"},{"answer":"11000000 10101000 00001010 00000101","incorrect":["10101010 10101010 10101010 10101010","11110000 00001111 11110000 00001111","11000100 11101000 01001010 00001011"],"question":"What is the binary representation of the IP address: 192.168.10.5 ?"},{"answer":"00001010 00010100 00011110 00101000","incorrect":["10101011 11001100 00101000 00101000","00001010 11110100 00011110 00101000","00111010 00010100 00011110 00101000"],"question":"Determine the binary representation of the IP address: 10.20.30.40 ?"}],"time":1800}